Abdul Rehman jutt

Lahore District, Punjab, Pakistan



arjprince807@gmail.com



+92323 4611 215



linkedin.com/in/abdul-rehman-jutt-8825b6228

Summary

I am an experienced Lead Generation Specialist with an extensive background in B2B and B2C lead generation and nurturing.

I specialize in identifying and targeting the right customers, creating leads, and converting them into sales. I have extensive knowledge of the lead generation process, including market research, lead generation tactics, segmentation, and data analysis. I am also highly knowledgeable in CRM software and have excellent communication skills.

I have a proven track record of success in lead generation and have consistently exceeded my client's goals. I am confident that I can create leads in a cost-effective way and help your business reach its full potential.

I am excited to discuss how my Lead Generation skills can help your business succeed. Please feel free to contact me.

Thank You!

Experience



Lead Generation Expert | Recruitment Resourcer | Web Researcher

BPO Solutions (Pvt) Ltd.

Jan 2021 - Present (2 years 10 months)

I have been working as a Recruitment Resourcer and Leads Generation Expert for 3 years in the Outsourcing & Offshore industry, I have much experience in Recruitment Resourcing, Leads Generation, Email Marketing, CV Sourcing, Company Mapping tasks, Client Mapping tasks, Email Generation, Business Development tasks, Finding B2B companies, and many other tasks, I have done this during my Service.

Recruitment Resourcer

Top Resourcing

Mar 2021 - Present (2 years 8 months)

- Talent Mapping & Market Mapping
- · Headhunting & Passive Search
- CV Sourcing & CV Formatting
- Research & Executive Search
- Administrative Support
- End-to-End Recruitment Support

M Lead Generation Expert

Top Marketing Media

Recruitment Resourcer | Lead Generation Expert

Top Resource Group Mar 2021 - Nov 2022 (1 year 9 months)

™ Web Researcher

Top Virtual Assistance Mar 2021 - Sep 2022 (1 year 7 months)

Education



National College Of Business Administration & Economics

Bachelor's of Science and Computer Science, Computer Science Oct 2021 - Jul 2023

Skills

Resourcing • Data Extraction • Spreadsheets • Teamwork • ONLINE RESEARCH • Headhunting • Passive Search • Market Mapping • Talent Mapping • Project Management